but the stock has been doing well ever
since but one of the stocks in the
broader Market is doing well since
yesterday our PB fintech hire in trade
this morning following on uh the gains
that it saw yesterday post policy bazars
partnership with ICICI Lombard Yash
joins in with more details on that story
Yash the stock continues to Rally well
uh that's correct mangam so last 15
minutes of yesterday's trading session
the stock pulled up about 15 bucks from
that particular point of announcement
and today that rally continues in the
morning it was up about 6% in trade uh
now the move that has come as far as PB
fintech is concerned is primarily based
on two important triggers one which came
just during the market close yesterday
and the other one which followed late in
the evening the first one is with
respect to an agreement between ICICI
Lombard and PB fintech uh now PB fintech
is the largest Insurance aggregator IC
Lombard is the largest private General
Insurance company and so far there was
no Synergy between these two large
players which is set to change with that
agreement all ICI Lombard products beat
motor Health travel home business
coverage will be available on policy
Bazar now an important part is that all
these products will be available both on
the online uh business of policy Bazar
that is policy bazar.com as well as the
offline business which is policy Bazar
platforms uh the reason why I say a very
large player comes on policy Bazar
because uh IC Lombard has almost 9%
market share when it comes to General
Insurance company collected about 25,000
CR in terms of premium in fi23 so of
course this augers very well for policy
Bazar in terms of the income or the
premium which it generates for ICA
Lombard also as well as the revenue
which it derives out of that assuming
25,000 CR annual premium which ICC
Lombard uh you know collected uh apart
from that the second trigger was
incorporation of a new subsidiary that
is uh PB pay that will be in payment a
payment agre Ator subsidiary now of
course the Market's been looking for new
ideas in terms of new revenue streams
which PB fintech would look to add and
this is an another addition as far as
that uh new income stream or new Revenue
stream is concerned uh this new
subsidiary under payment agregation
business has been Incorporated under PB
fintech now uh this subsidiary will
apply for a license from RBI and once
that license is received payment
aggregation business under the
subsidiary which will fall under pbtech
would be initiated okay thanks a lot for
that Yash well just